I'm over the record, I'm going to say the Council meeting for Monday, October 7, 2024.
All right, so you're going to tell me at this name.
Just like a movie.
That's not enough?
I don't want to say to anybody, are you looking at me?
I don't want to tell anybody.
I don't want to get wrong.
But a proclamation, I'm telling you, October 224, has.
That's not enough, man.
All right.
That's enough.
These two.
I'm going to see you.
Put them inside.
Oh, that's enough.
All right.
Hello.
I'm going to see you.
I heard you're going to watch the last movie.
One.
Voice.
I'm going to have to sound in on me on time.
Are you going to listen to me?
No.
You're going to listen to support me.
All right.
What?
Speak on the one is going to be in the back of the tree.
Good!
How to dam up?
I was on a scale of extreme.
Try Xarotud.
I don't have Xarotud.
I mean, I just never heard about the water.
I've got to turn the water in the bed.
If you don't have the water, I'll turn the water in the bed.
Okay.
Sorry, please.
Your name's fine.
I'm out.
Yeah, I'm out.
God help.
Thank you.
Okay, Ron, me, man.
Oh, I'm chugging you.
Okay.
are you interested?
I'll be the winner.
I do want to thank you.
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
You're welcome.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Nice to be back.
I'm Dr. Nixon.
Thank you.
Good.
I'm Dr. Funham.
user, Charles Hood, and Patrick Lambert for their military service.
I wish you a good work.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm going to go.
And please, please.
The veterans.
If you're on the right deck.
Mr.
So if you want to tell a little bit about what you're going to do.
Sure.
So both here may not be enough.
I just don't know what we just did.
I mean, I need to.
Yes.
I want to.
Thank you.
I'm going to count.
This is our city here.
We're going to parallel our veterans in the city of my aunt.
And for the past 16 years, the city of my aunt is going to be a great perfect entry to these people like you should retreat.
We can't be here for actually starts to start on holiday in the 31st.
We have it through that week weekend.
And everything is provided for them.
We, we, we, uh, it's really not about hunting.
We've killed it here.
It's about the camaraderie.
And, uh, and let them know that small small town America loves our veterans.
And we know where our freedom comes from.
And we know who sacrificed for that freedom.
And, uh, it's a unique event.
It's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a spiritual thing.
And, uh, it's a, it's a project.
And it's pretty obvious.
Uh, the banquet, uh, actually, uh, it starts at nine o'clock.
It's a traumatized school.
And, uh, there's a, there's a, uh, a school life, simply, uh, all of our sacred percentage of being there.
And I got a little, uh, bless you early there.
Uh, give you some kind of a warmth.
Or the, uh, the veterans in the ranking.
Nice.
Uh, it's a, uh, it's a, uh, it's a heartwarming event.
And it's, uh, it shows the world.
When we think of our veterans, and when we think of our freedom,
And it's become a small town of America.
It happens nowhere else in the whole world.
And it's pretty, it happens in, uh, my own home and commerce.
Thank you very much for being part of it.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right.
It's good to get out of this fellowship alone.
It gives us an opportunity to say thank you for those guys.
I will say
Just to say everybody knows, all of the events, there's a schedule on Facebook, if you go to the River Bottom Sportsman page, all of the mills that we do on Friday and Saturday are open to the public.
You can come hang out, eat with us, and visit with the veteran owners. They'd love to see you.
So we hope that you come out and we'll make sure you get fit well.
The banquet is at Buckle Run, start at 6 o'clock on Thursday evening on the 31st. Everyone here is welcome.
Just come and join them and eat with them and I think you'll enjoy the event. It's a good thing to read this.
And he wouldn't get in the way he's at the spiritual event. If you go to that, that change your heart.
I've been there and seen it, seen the joy of the faces and a lot of the guys are learning. They need somebody just to love them.
But they're loving and jacked out. He's a lover and a great guy. He really is. He ordered art and soul in this thing, so appreciate what he does for you.
And that meal out of his place without saying that.
So thank you guys both for what you do.
All right, four book and book. Let's get the personal appearances. We have them.
Bye. Plain's list.
Perfect.
10 minutes.
He says 10 minutes.
6 minutes.
From the September 16th to 2024.
And September 23rd, 2024.
That's perfect.
10 minutes.
He's still.
Jones.
So presentation by the Bridges Foundation.
I'm not great now.
Thank you.
Thank you guys for letting us come.
I'm from the British Foundation.
And I'm from the British Foundation.
So we are one of those willing bridges for the British Affairs.
The British Foundation was started in 1964.
We were just celebrated our 60th anniversary.
My group of parents who wanted a place in their loved ones to put disabilities to gain
vocational training for life skills and increase in benefits.
Our mission is to enhance a quality of life for adults with barriers and families in our community
and training education when the services are happening.
Our mission is to provide a foundation of the place for every individual's diverse or purpose in the world.
We're just currently served 400 individuals annually.
We partner with 12 different school districts, 16 community partnerships, 16 community
employment contracts, we have seven program programs, three facilities, and 52 employees,
employment coaches, and these are ages, ten years, two retired.
So we're going to start by training, um, services are training programs, um, we have EDS,
EDS connections, um, transportation counseling, and for regular, any type of therapy
with their speech in school, um, therapy, occupational therapy, um, we provide advocacy
to have actors to see programs, for all these individuals, um, and then we also provide
a pre-vocational training for space learning, center programs, um, starting at the age
of the 18th and we teach them to also build the same factor in the production of 3DL and hospitality.
Um, our deal with training is education, experience, and empowerment.
Um, employment services, we, um, offer manufacturing and times for services, three services
in the many more retail, um, our benefits is, we want them to have competitive, um, integrated wages,
um, ongoing support for personal job coach, they learn skillfully, can't say.
Um, we do help with their job search, play some follow-up services counseling, um, and, um,
um, what's with their mentor, um, we're just actually actually have our own manufacturing and
co-opers' outsourcing, um, manufacturing will be the infrastructure parts for ICO, which is, um,
um, a plant across from Tulsa Airport, um, PD-Waytonton's running to the make-see managed by the, um,
guilty, um, a lot of Tulsa manufacturing, they can't contact us.
We build their parts to be some of that, they send it to the budget shareholder.
Um, we also have our VR.
Program, which is what we have started in the way, um, you're actually office, um, at the chamber,
downtown, and 11,000, um, our vocational relocation, um, program is great, it's growing, um,
and so we are excited. Um, we get this more organization in the achievements of last year.
You have your government to work for employability, of any of the year, and job coach of the year.
And November, next month, we are going back to the government's office because we wanted,
again, the year for all free categories.
Um, partying on purpose, either some of our partners, um, like I said, we're based out of James Tulsa
area, so these are the current. We are expanding for, um, building workers.
So, um, I am an American recyclers, data trainers, um, abskow, the softwares,
norm, um, our own Hudson, so we're building work bridges, um,
expanding opportunities, the resources to serve more, um, building bridges in my Amazon, um,
June of this year, we are going to purchase the board of interactive counsel.
Um,
They want to best reach out to you guys too as well.
And you're kind of what it takes to bring for just my month.
We say great.
August 24th, we long shared VR program here.
We're actively completing intakes on science
and we are accepting side assessment locations.
So side assessment locations are not asking there's a booth
if they would participate in letting our job coaches
or clinical consults bring an individual there.
Let them do assessment for by seeing visual action
and monitoring services, things like that.
And possibly, employees and individuals as well.
Our community, our current community training partnerships
are emerging in the mics.
I'm a public library in the orthopedes in the gym.
And the donkeys did in the last days, you got during the parks.
So we're continuing to grow.
We're still facing seven at the worst of the year.
So today's things.
We got off the economic services.
Autotank and Appulation are being held approximately.
Our regional employment rates, 15, unemployment rate,
an autonomous burden point two of as a Bachelor of 20.
Very simple in it.
It's just kind of disability, transportation, homelessness.
Mental health.
Whether it's anxiety, depression.
A disability, emotion.
A learning barrier.
A criminal barrier.
Posted incarceration.
And post-bright groups.
In high school students.
Put the barrier.
So when we go back and training programs.
We have a work of just a training program that we partner
with all the schools.
We have a work of just a training program that we partner.
We get juniors and seniors in high school.
They come spend four hours a day with our block teachers.
And they learn their job skills.
So that was when they did learn their high school.
They have a job in the community.
So just kind of a little head start.
So this is kind of what a process looks like for a client.
They go to the intake process.
They can act with their employment counsel.
They act as a fleet to size assessment.
Whether it's car fishing, bushing, whatever their job is.
And that is a DLS requirement.
So they go to vocational presence in the 18 training.
With their athletic counsel.
Interview is field filling out applications.
Building resume.
And they go back over here.
Good job placement.
There's play set of jobs.
We call up four weeks.
We call up eight weeks.
After that, they are considered a job stabilization.
And successful 90 days of employment.
And then their life span of that job.
Our employment counsel saves what's up.
So they are never just your employees.
So they stay with their community to check you on.
So I'm going to spot you here.
So what that, I know this gets to be a little bit confusing.
But at a 50,000.
what that means is that we excel so when we go back to the disability, the governor's
award, what they, what they have said to us is that you do really well at what you do.
You're talking to the state and this is what we're talking to the state and that is right
here for the span of the job, but no, not only that, for a lifetime, so if they work up Walmart
and then they go to Roberts and Tire, they go with them.
If they go for Roberts and Tire to a boutique, we go with them.
Wherever they go, for the rest of their life, until they retire, we go with them.
I was saying earlier, 60% of the individuals that we serve have been with bridges for 47
years.
Lulu is 67 years old, Wilbert is in his early 70s and he has been with us since he graduated
high school.
So we don't get paid for it, we don't get reimbursed, you say, well, how do you do that?
Kylie's a development, a grant writer, she writes grants, we have a $2.6 million annual budget
and for a fundraiser.
That's not, I mean, it's good for us.
We tighten our belt because every dye that we get, whether it's our service or whether
it's our contracts, we do manufacturing contracts and all of those contracts, everything that
we do, we've diversified our revenue so we can serve more people.
It's not just a circle, come in the door, get your brochure and walk out, come in the door, get
a job and leave.
It's family, it's personal to us and we want to help you.
And I have to work until we're retired, so today and we want to be able to advocate and to
be with them.
So this is, this is fine whenever you think, okay, as an individual who's getting services, what
does that mean?
We're going to be with you every single step of the way, but when your job responds ability changes,
I'm going to go in and I'm going to be an admin.
Well, now I get to go over here and be a clerk, we're going to step back in and help train you.
Well, now and not only am I going to get to be a clerk, I get to go and do this job.
We're going to step back in and train you.
We're going to walk you through the steps of that job and if that job is something that you are satisfied
but you want to move on to another employer, we won't leave you.
I mean, it's personal, and we want to be the advocate for that individual, because that is what
success is for you and for me is that we have an advocate and I think our community, I think
we try to educate our community and let them know that there is value, everybody is somebody.
So we do have an advocate program for the community and for institutions and it's okay to hire somebody
with the disability or a barrier.
We educate, we strive to educate the community.
We're not only trying our approach, we're sitting here trying to train you, but we also
train the community on.
It's okay.
What barriers are you having?
Are you concerned?
Is it an insurance liability?
What is it that you have questions about?
Let us train you.
We do pretty good.
So, why is it that you have to graduate in employment services?
We have 90% success rate and long-term sustainable job places.
We receive ongoing support from our employment consult, increase overall productivity for businesses.
State businesses and initial costs and new employee onboarding.
We sell jobs, vacancies with different employees, and it's free of charge to start businesses.
So, businesses do not pay for our services.
And we fill those jobs that they can see by, we get them set up on their own transportation.
If transportation is a barrier, we make sure to take a transportation to be able to do that job.
So, we have a video to show.
I cry every time I watch it.
Yeah, I feel like watching it.
I think it's three minutes.
Boy coming to work because everybody is somebody and everybody deserves the best.
And everybody deserves a chance to be the best.
And who will lose 67% of the children?
I think that's the 25 years to the individuals that we start.
Because it's important.
Hey, now she's been with us for 40 plus years.
Regents is a great place to come to work.
We're individuals with barriers to employment.
It is an opportunity for them to learn skills to learn a paycheck and to be in a supportive environment.
For an employer, it is a great opportunity for you to have a relationship or a partnership with a company that can kid, package, ship, complete your orders in a timely manner with quality.
Sure it's attached to it.
And for families, it is an opportunity for you to feel good that you're left on your side, your daughter, your brother, your sister has a path.
A journey that you'd be independent in self-sufficiency.
We have a building, a crew, a team of people who are supportive and caring, kind, and
their certain hearts, and I think that makes bridges the success that we are today.
It's just surrounding ourselves with a really good, strong, kind people who want the best
work they're ever.
And I think the work everyday is it's a blessing, we get to serve, and this is the mission,
and we're able to fill it in daily, and some way, even if it is just the time, it's
just helping someone and learning to task or something, it is making an impact on a local
company and the community with providing jobs in growing our workforce.
You know that you're not just helping the one individual that you're working with, but it's
their entire family, and they're lovely that as well, because when they're able to come
here at the nurse's family, they will go work and know and have peace of mind that they're
one safe with us.
Coming in, I just wanted a place where she was safe, and did really better if she made any money or, you
know, that was at the point the point was for her, she was safe and for her to have something
to do, and it's going to be far exceeded that, because not only was she safe, she enjoyed
what she did, has made many new friends, and has really exceeded and what we ever thought.
Possibly.
Now, I have a story, I can do it like three or four trades of dog trades now, thanks me,
I feel like I'm proud of myself to do stuff like that, it's so proud of myself, and
she's long been here for like a long, long time, and I don't remember me in this place.
We're all better having together so much, so we're like three and like so, it's four and then
a job, and it's four and a job that I'm going to rent, and she looks forward to having
every day.
It's a little doggy, it's a little doggy, it's a little doggy, it's a little doggy, it's
a little doggy here.
Everyone have a happy year, I'm happy.
Often, I get the calls from employees and employee at another company saying we worked with you
over here on this project in the 11th and you can go to a talk to us after a short period
of time, and it puts them on the end, they quickly write them out.
They realize that the barriers are not there, that they originally got.
These guys are awesome, they work hard, they strive to be successful, so working with them
is just been...
I mean, to help someone along the way, you know, who's come to us, not knowing whether they can work or, you know, having any confidence to now coming in and doing a job and doing it right.
It's funny when I started being into their organization that we could get into a hatchback and a high school here.
And I don't know why it is fun having them around to help me learn myself more because I haven't done a job in my side of the family.
So, it is fun to have more people, more friends along the way that have our sisters to keep me going.
But just have me to come in a better job.
So, I'm a well-struck customer system.
I help customers to get their dates or take them to Christmas, to open lunches.
I appreciate it with Mr. McEat that was Mr. McEat.
With Mr. McEat and the other British members helped me find this job because this is my third job.
And I wanted this job to help people to come together and we don't know about this.
I think it just brings us into warmth and it just really cares down barriers.
I know people ask what it is and what we do and the very next words are come see.
Because once you come see you get it, it's hope and it's a lifeline for families.
British is pretty fancy.
Everyone is unique and everyone requires a different approach and we have the ability to get that.
We work to identify this skills needed to achieve the goals that are desired in that aspect.
It makes bridges in the old. Everybody is so funny.
It's a funny question.
We want to love with you. We want to work with your families.
You're community work inclusive.
One family.
These guys are special. They are special to us.
And I know that they're special to you.
And we just want to help you as a family.
Get our loved ones together so they can be achieving their goals for a lifetime.
Go.
Yeah, I have any questions.
I know this is overwhelmed.
This is some of our princesses.
Save a lot on the box for changing cases.
Gas stations.
That clinic, Chatters.
The basic press.
Our washroom.
The people.
We help their.
They.
Girls.
And then testimony is made to each of the operation majors,
which is a free attitude of sort of a perfect job,
watching men, learning a ballot, with mayors,
that upheld the joy for the whole team,
and for various school districts that are providing peace and money
in our students and for participating in a different plan.
And it organized programs, both this on and this in a kind of way of the point.
We also partnered with Pepsi, out of all of those as well.
So I'm going to board and move that phone.
I'm going to play there as well.
And to watch you on.
Don't we appreciate you guys coming out.
The next one is, I hope you all have a great day.
We'll be back with you.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for having us.
Thank you.
Well, we'll be back with you.
Wait, you guys for your afternoon.
This is part of the process.
Thank you.
You got to play, right?
We do.
So we were talking to you about manufacturing jobs.
And in 2010, we purchased a boutique in jeans.
And at our boutique, you saw Ms. Kaila Sheet,
that talked about our dog treats.
We have, I have mentioned about diversifying our revenue.
One of the businesses that we created in 2013,
with the Bridges Barkerie, which is for my dog treats.
The next one that we produce is the Bridges Popcorn at the Bridges Market
Teal, along with the Bridges outsourcing.
And those sources are ready to help us provide more services to more individuals.
But we sell the popcorn for fundraisers, for parties.
We do give a thanks for your special events.
We say purchase with the purpose.
When you purchase a item from the market teal,
or through a fundraising event, it is with the purpose.
So you're giving a gourmet item.
And you're also providing employment to someone with a barrier to them.
They brought all the counsel by the popcorn and supper pump,
but they gave him dog treats.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Award Q24 back 90,
certificate of the positive grant.
We'll see you in about $1 million.
$3,000.
Please create a bag to your related signing family,
or your submitted or his business.
Right?
I'm here to the council.
We saw the CD, the highest amount of money that I'm sure need to purchase
6th half a CD, and then now the number of three.
And we request the quotes from four financial institutions.
And...
of the price, is that came man-langed from 26,130 up to 27,820.
Security back in trust was the ones that we've been offered
in 27,820.
They came in and gave us a 4.28% and our best was the next
closest and came in at 4.106.
And we recommend purchasing the 4.28 from Security back in trust,
and we need your approval.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Thank you, sir.
Approach in a blender.
Very good.
There we go.
That was also very good.
From some seven-mile stone, your blade signing,
and the thing with authority is to see man-langored.
Thank you.
So, what we're going to do now is we're questions from the people
of Congress, and we're going to talk to where you can.
You can remember here a few months back.
It's going to be, and that we brought you to the field scale.
We'll just show you all these new things that we've introduced.
So, we went out for RFP.
We got two back.
I've heard close to the situation.
We're going to do a number of different things.
We decided to go with the...
What can sense at the bottom of the zone?
I think it gets all of the meat, and it'll serve to you for a long time out there.
I think that it's less expensive than before.
Yeah.
I'll tell you.
Really, how we're getting into the guide of this,
for a living?
We're going to have to have a step off for a review on it.
So, what are you going to do out there?
You're going to go just to the west, and we're going to carry it with you.
What are we going to have?
Yes.
And that's a little bit like that.
Not actually a picture of here.
It's what we showed you is the tribe.
I think that's a nice cool.
Yeah.
So, we're going to show you a little bit of an artillery.
What is it?
It's all in the middle of the century.
It's the more cost effective way to be placed out.
You think that there will be a good estimate.
If you look at it moving forward with the crevations,
which things are perhaps not all ready to go.
six hundred and ten on the picture for the RFP that they sent us, but I don't mind if they've just
a template. So on the...
Yeah, so what you had, you had six hundred and ten crannies in the place in the Auschwitz
part of the collection that have an additional hundred and twenty doors on the exterior of it.
So on the three sides of the hundred and twenty, which you could put two, two yards each
one of that, so two hundred and forty on the exterior of this custody additional six hundred
and ten on the outward. But it gives the public capacity that you can convert to fifty,
which is above beyond what we originally have that.
That's what we have. In addition to this, we are...
We're looking at the purchase aid. We call it the more the wall, which is provided
from the Santa Fe. And that would be where anybody who's placed into that
and that ought to be where we're gathering seven areas on that,
and that would be part of the heritage of the Auschwitz.
We need to buy it to be a great need for us to be in charge of this building.
You need to be in charge of this building?
Yes, we need to.
To improve that, just as part of this.
Great choice.
On the two of us, we're looking at the board tremendously.
We're looking at the committee and we're looking at the board.
We're looking at the board.
Thank you.
For tremendously, we're looking at the board.
We're looking at the board.
And bringing it to my point.
The influence of our committee.
I'm very pleased to meet you guys.
Very pleased.
Thank you.
that there have been some questions and some answers and meetings going back and forth.
So this is the same contract, there have been no changes.
It's the $46,000 for the call and answer of this here in Miami.
It helps support them.
It is 2% of their budget, it makes up 2%, their budget is 2.5 million to actually earn this year.
Yeah, because I am here.
I am here if you have questions.
We have to try to answer them in Miami.
I'm not going to tell you in practice, but my answer is going to be in here to go to you.
And I know that you are going to answer that.
I know that you are going to answer that.
You are a little bit of a person.
Yeah.
One of the changes from last year to this year is the requirement for COVID-19.
We are not driving.
I have not.
We don't have a contract.
I did ask for.
I haven't heard back yet.
Okay.
Well, I brought some staff to the community.
I was understanding that they were sending them to use.
No, go on up.
Okay.
That's true.
So, what did you think?
Did you like to thank you for the last being that we were going to start posting in the
Quarterly Prior to the contract.
It's not.
It's a different matter.
Yeah.
And I will say that we met, we met in July, so we would have just had that portion.
So we were just, I asked them to hand them to be just before this meeting, but I thought
that they were sending them as well, just before this meeting.
So they may have not got to push up EU and may have not gotten pushed up EU, but I didn't
want them to be in it.
And with that said, the trumps are up from him and he met last time about 20% of that.
Yeah.
And when the revenue miles are at 550 and I can have the thing about that, we're doing your
presentation as well.
Overall, the total stats that we've taken 3036 or 3632 trips in this last quarter.
And that is July 1, 2013.
So total revenue miles were 31,966 in the region within the city was 770,709 and 3.
And with that, it doesn't end the top number, because the pitch, which is our after-hour
operation as well.
And I know that we talked and we met about doing a heat map, so I asked them to start down.
We're a indicator.
Yeah.
So they are still working on that.
This is tiny, because I can turn it out on my phone, on my phone, on my phone.
Friends report.
So we're going to be able to provide some data.
And basically, what we've got right now shows the locations, kind of generalized locations
within the city where people are going to be.
It doesn't provide specific addresses.
It's just kind of showing like those general areas.
like I've been looking at it from here and saying Walmart is pretty hot.
You know, that's true.
It's a good way.
Well, those blood pressure attention that they were, they were strong.
Pumped again.
Um, they were having trouble with coordinating pickups.
And it was in on our effort.
Don't worry for the direct info.
These was to how can we better help this development in that area.
So do we need a schedule?
Hey, you know, a nine times pickup.
And it's 10 o'clock every day or two.
Then we can take it in a trial count.
And maybe they can schedule a pickup somewhere.
That helps their citizens look at terms where we can work with you to help our citizens get something.
So that's what the happens.
Right.
And that's kind of what we're trying to dig out this status for you.
Um, so, like I said, if you haven't done these at you, look at them.
Okay.
So.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Well, they're going to do it.
Well, I know that it was cool.
But they couldn't do it together.
Okay.
I'll make sure you get it.
Yeah.
No problem.
There are any other questions.
And I will need to come up and answer any questions.
Or try to answer any questions.
Certainly get you to answer any questions.
Because I, as the extent to the director, you know, I over see several programs that
not at that lower level.
And I, like you said, I'm on the box.
And I'm on the box.
We're not going to have a meeting.
Yeah.
We're going to take it.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm going to ask.
Okay.
Thank you.
So.
Okay.
Thank you.
I don't want to say.
You know we have struggled us with this for a while, but I want you to know that your efforts have helped us overcome this and we appreciate you being a good partner for us.
Yeah, well I look forward to a long partnership. I know that a lot of people can do together. Even, I mean, I can't help it.
I think we're headed in the right direction. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm a budget member of 25.
That's your six creating a scene on a senior center.
Budget, Canadian proposed revenue and expenses.
So this is one of three agenda items that we're going to see in your center.
Ever since I was 20, I was 29.
I'm going to have to go to a management of the senior center.
So it's been a...
very rebevered on doing all these things.
I know can't have their many times publicly.
And it was Cindy's work with the personnel,
and I'm paperwork.
I worked with Jennifer on the budget.
So this is the budget, this creates the revenues
and expenditures.
It does, I do want to point out that the 24,000
that we normally pay that to the senior center
is actually just being transferred to this fund
from the digital fund.
It does include, so we'll get right to talk
about two branches, it does include
that I said we would receive them
and we'll go over there.
So it's very real quick.
We mentioned everybody involved.
Thank you to all of you guys.
It was the tough process that we had to come to up here
and the senior, we had to come to knowing everything
we know now, but you absolutely all did the exact right thing.
And I appreciate all of you guys being patient,
buying in and helping us get to this process.
Thank you all.
I like you all.
Jennifer?
Margaret.
Michael?
He's deaf, but.
Jim's.
12.
The budget made with 25 national 07.
We increased revenue and expense.
The new airport terminal, a lot of city to pay.
Cross on a $49,000, $47,48.
And directly for pay.
Appetitians 1 and 2.
We're seeing an expense for $90,000,
and $20,000, and $30,000.
It's actually all good.
So let money, we're seeing an expense for $30,000.
It's been in 3.3,000 national and an element of the arts.
A big read grant for the literacy program, literacy program.
And decreased rates, paying for a pair budget to correct them out,
due to late payment.
$1,6 million.
That's for this year, 23, 24.
So I do want to point out that the late payment.
It was a late expense in the last year.
So we have to estimate what carryover is.
And April, June, May, June.
And there was a payment on June 30th that course we couldn't know about.
So that just corrects the expenditures that were approved
in 23, 24 to a lot of that balance system.
And that should save you money.
And then it's also for the grant for the library.
It's the opioid settlement money.
Which it is bringing in.
It is extending out.
But there's going to have to be a committee.
And we have to go over the grant to get the details about what
I think it's standardized and was really specific.
And then the other thing is on the airport.
And if a paperwork was not completed.
So we have to...
across $495,000, so we can make it.
So Barbara asked, we pay them directly,
and then the right way to reverse us person.
That's a wonderful question.
Can we talk about the airport in the library
and all the same action I have?
Because these are things that the canceled is important.
If you can initiate, I would be talking to you
with your ministry.
I would be talking to you about DL.
We all have a fight.
I would be talking to you, and we are about
the whole thing.
But these are all the funds that the canceled
of groups and managers.
Are you going to accept it?
No, I'm going to go.
I just was curious why they're all together.
And then also we mentioned that we're going to be
in a reverse that that the garbage is not in this action.
I have an extended, we're going to be in reverse
with the total of $495.
On the minute itself, it says, once I'll
FAA grant documents are executed,
Garber will coordinate a reverse into the city
from the full amount of the FAA that's $42.
That's actually a minute.
So that's a question.
That's a question too.
Something too.
On the minute.
We actually send them to the state.
Once our year ends, I'm not sure why.
We send them our budget.
But we also send them to the end of the year pass.
So instead of sending 150, we have to send them to the end.
Just curious.
Yeah.
I know that.
Um, this, so we, we're going to open it.
Um, with council, we're going to see those broken up in the bit.
I'm going to respond.
None of those going to create more.
I just, I just was curious about that.
Um, 13 community.
Expansion and attrition and attrition and attrition and attrition.
Assistants.
See you at Y25 grant application through grant gateway for the Mindless
Senior Center.
I'll proceed.
Mayor to some.
So the next two are the last two for the senior center.
Um, the senior grant is for two purposes one.
It's $2,000 just for general operations.
Um, that would supply like a general portal utilities.
I'm going to use your phone, communication expenses, offices, expenses.
Um, the other part is for 600, 100, there's for clients.
And they're planning on.
Um, the next day you'll see.
Um, 75,000 dollars.
They're going to create a kitchen area.
It's going to be a.
the cracker, which is the northeast corner of the building. If you see the pool room, it's
perpendicular to the pool room. They're going to kind of door in, so you can go to the
kitchen from the pool room. So if there's a turntant, then you can go there instead of the main
part of the building. But that, if there's 6,500 floor appliances, they're playing on by a stove
and a hood, a refrigerator, dishwasher, and then other small things as the money allows,
maybe I think you're a priori or more than two things like that.
The member came in there because it was under an issue with that side, but the air
not flowing properly or something over there, that was the same. Is that going to be able to be?
This one helped that.
Okay. Yeah, that's right. That's what helped that.
Okay. Thank you.
14. Royal Economic Action Plan and Reap.
This year, 24 grant application through Green Gateway, the non-seekers Center
for Food Relation, CC 2020, 24 National Avenue, Authorizing Application, financial
assistance from the rural economic action plan.
So this is for $75,000. They're inversely approached us with this, which we're very thankful for.
Again, it'll create the machinery in the craft room and access to the pool room.
Other things are going to be included. That's $75,000.
And you signage and solve carteting and flooring. That's about $13,000.
A tribute to that. You kind of do a bathroom refresh, purchase an additional TV
besides the one that just purchased.
Replacing the untiled paint.
Do some inspections of the main paint on the upside and the roof.
Maybe some 900 shares, re-verbished the pool tables.
And then paint pool room and really training that.
Just as far as the money will go, we're going to use the construction and the property.
Is it good?
It's good.
Just at the park.
The nearest one was talking about, thank you.
Because whenever we're talking about doing all this, we're used to that.
Then we get this on, you do this and we appreciate you falling through.
And give you this great part of course.
Okay.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
15.
I hope you can manage these grant agreement for $25 dollars for preservation of the
genealogy collection.
That's the mine.
We'll put the library all for us if you manage or sign.
Okay.
So we apply for this grant for local home.
If you may be, isn't also do our let's talk about it.
Brayette's.
And one that helps us with this.
And then we're just $2,500 dollars.
So begin the process.
process of scanning our unique items that are in genealogy, something like history.
We have all kinds of stuff over there.
Hundreds of books, but this will just get us started.
Some of my scanners, two different types of scanners,
hands and storage, thanks online.
That we can host for this one.
People will be able to access it.
And you're saying this is just our county?
Yes.
It's a good piece of county.
When we got a quote to ask somebody to come into this forest,
it was over 70,000 dollars.
So this is our way of trying to do it ourselves.
Some kind of a half-assed,
or how we will get done more in the track.
Mr. Brun.
He stood above.
John's trying to get towards the country.
Thank you.
16, the ordinance amending to subvert graph two.
It's both a piece, a waste, it's both a facility.
It's actually getting to break the chapter point,
the facility.
The total support is providing some ability,
providing for conflicting provisions,
building all the facilities.
It's absolutely effective to date increasing tipping fees
and solid waste facility.
I'm out of there.
I'm going to start off.
Yes, Council.
As we talked before, we're talking about increasing tipping fees.
For the in-house or the 75% economic impact
is between 11 and 6, and then seven,
one, and one, and go to 8, and 10,
are at a reasonable rate of $85 per ton,
and then 90, that day with $50,000,
our ad state will go to the 105 per ton.
And at 110, it's 25,000,
and all those.
This was to cover as we talked to you,
and we had that study done.
We always cover her across,
and we're going to toss on that, this is to insert some of our policy.
This is so we can say that publicly first, the camera, in the case of my mother's back, looks
this cleaner and wants to go all the way to raise this.
I agree with her ways of this, because right now we're losing money every month, because it's
costing us more to dispose of the trash that it is, but we're bringing it.
That's correct.
You know, with our, just our, depends on the month you look at,
but how much, you know, transportation means that the,
the care for the transportation itself in the landfill,
we're sitting somewhere around $50.
$60.50 a dollar per turn.
So just in that cost, you will see the recovery.
I don't really call it slow.
I'm so messed up.
And that wasn't counting the labor that we had in the transfer station in our equipment,
that we went to.
That was just our costs.
Did you get what that was?
My promotion approved.
There were two.
Sir?
Isn't that both?
No.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Hello, thanks.
Welcome.
Thank you.
And we have all of the bill back.
And we are at this town of St. Martin.
Thank you.
going up this Saturday night, right, 40 goals, I'm right, zero, let's go.
Is there a ride, 40 goals in the middle of Ane Street, right from Poland?
There's our goal, the whole ride arena on Wednesday night, and by Saturday there's a ride
and a goal, and then a B-Live on the Cowboy Channel, Cowboy Channel, Cowboy Network.
But we kind of pulled that out right in the middle of the 66, so we don't know if any other way
happened anywhere, we were open to growth, growing next year, making it a little bigger and better.
But let's see how I do this year.
I probably don't love people at all, I don't know what I can, but he's really pumped up by it.
So, you know that this last weekend is in the old homecoming, and counsel is all that gathered
with the service of putting the people with the full of it when we give us time to get out of the public.
So, it was nice there, and I got to show up, and I ended up just for a little while.
And of course, everybody has other stuff to do to run, and put all the games on the screen, so he showed up a little while on that.
There's a good bit in the middle.
Main Street dinner is coming up.
Good night, James.
Thank you.
Good night.
Good night, James.
What's your name?
No, I was just 18.
That's what I'm freaking out about.
I mean, you said you said you said you said you think it's valuable?
Yeah, we do.
We do.
But all we like to want to do is go.
So, so, Aaron, if you have been there, you need to come there.
It's really cool here.
Oh.
But then, we're going to tell you right now, Main Street.
We're also going to put it in the other.
It's cool here.
You guys didn't come.
And see what?
It's been getting that work.
You guys did.
So, 20 tickets left.
So, last time.
They're going to go.
So, he's going to go.
They're not going to go.
They're going to go.
So, he's going to go or not.
I want to go.
Can you go?
No.
He's not going to go.
If you can, I'll go.
Go through that first time.
Woo.
I was going to go.
I think.
I thought you ran like 30.
I thought I'm like 30.
Well, that might.
On Thursday.
That's the only thing.
I think we're still still.
I think it's a cab.
It's a cranky, not a lot.
All right, it's the 20th city manager communication.
I'm also the, we have to do all parade, which is under the city, the MSG, what I would
be able to, they're in the community of Triggas.
Oh, really?
Cool.
I don't know the answer.
My overall seat there, so I'm a community who are in the city here, but it's good.
And then also, then we want to point out, in the packet of BCA, collections that were on the
stage for that at 6.1, so we can name that on Tuesdays, and then there's some of the
things that I can do, you know, to do it at the time.
I think they have to, I think they have to, so a bit of community that we got that deal done
by and so, yeah, so we want to do another one.
Do it.
Good morning.